roveconcepts.com 2017-06-16

# Privacy Policy | Rove Concepts

  * 

From time to time, we here at Rove Concepts will update our privacy statement based on the feedback we receive, and we’ll be sure to let you know by adding the word "Updated" next to our Privacy Policy link. It’s a good idea to take a peek at the changes, so you know how we’re protecting your information when you buy from us. If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policy or updates, don’t hesitate to contact our customer service department at [customercare@roveconcepts.com](mailto:customercare@roveconcepts.com)

When you place an order with us, we might ask for some personal information, like your name, shipping address, telephone number, e-mail address, billing address, credit card number and expiration date. We use this information to:

  * Process an order
  * Verify your identity for payment authorization
  * Contact you regarding your order status
  * Ship your order to you
  * Allow you to apply for financing ( _coming soon)_
  * Send you news from Rove Concepts (if you have requested it)
  * Provide you with an excellent shopping experience

When you place an order with Rove Concepts, we'll transfer your name and address to your credit card company for confirmation to complete your purchase, and then to the third-party fulfillment center to deliver your order. We promise to never use your name and address for any other purpose, including selling it to mailing-list firms. Sometimes we do share blanket information and statistics about our customers with important business partners, but we’ll never reveal your individual details.

The AdRoll platform uses cookies, tracking pixels and related technologies to provide our services for Advertisers. Cookies are small data files that are served by our platform and stored on your device. They enable us to identify your device when you move between different websites and applications, so that we can serve targeted advertising to you.

Specifically, the AdRoll cookie we serve through the AdRoll platform for this purpose is named “__adroll”. We may also drop an additional AdRoll opt-out cookie if you opt-out as described below. We may also drop cookies from our Advertising Partners for the purposes described above. The Advertising Partner cookies dropped vary by Advertiser implementation.

Occasionally, we might ask you if you’d like to participate in a completely voluntary survey. The information you give us is entirely up to you and typically includes your first name, along with a review of your Rove Concepts experience and a review of the products you purchase. We use this survey information to improve the shopping experience for you and your fellow customers. Some answers might be posted on our site to provide information about our products to other users, only after you give your permission. We promise to always ask and notify you before sharing any of your individual details and information with our third-party friends.

  * If you’d rather not hear from us, we won't take it personally! Just hit “unsubscribe” on our subscription status page and enter your information. You can also opt out by emailing us at [customercare@roveconcepts.com](mailto:customercare@roveconcepts.com)
  * You can opt-out of receiving targeted ads served by us or other advertising companies: AdRoll is also a member of the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) and adheres to the NAI Code of Conduct. You may use the NAI opt out tool [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/), which will allow you to opt out of seeing targeted ads from us and from other NAI approved member companies.

We also comply with the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising as managed by the Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA). You may opt out of receiving targeted ads from other companies that perform ad targeting services, including some that we may work with as Advertising Partners via the DAA website [here](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).

We also adhere to the European Interactive Advertising Digital Alliance (EDAA) guidelines for online advertising and you may opt out via their [Your Online Choices website](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/).

Here at Rove Concepts, we’re committed to protecting your privacy and personal information. Whenever you submit information -- including your credit card number, name, and address -- to the Roveconcepts.com e-commerence system via your computer, it’s encrypted using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software. At our headquarters, we also use encryption and Web security technologies to protect your privacy and personal data. Only parties responsible for processing your order will have access to your credit card and bank information. We at Rove Concepts constantly review our policies and practices to ensure that all of your information remains safe and secure.

 **Contacting Rove Concepts**

We want to make sure your customer service experience is as high-quality as our furniture. There are always multiple ways to ask questions and provide feedback.

Directly contact a Rove Concepts consultant by email either via the "Contact Us" link or writing to [customercare@roveconcepts.com](mailto:customercare@roveconcepts.com). We always read every email and try to answer your questions as quickly as possible. You can also call us at 800-705-6217. We may use your comments to improve the site and service, or review and discard the information. We also love to hear your comments and feedback about the website or your shopping experience, and sincerely welcome any testimonials about our service or products.

Don't worry -- you are protected if a third party perpetrates credit card fraud using your personal information from a Rove Concepts purchase.

The only time we’ll share your personal information is when required by law or with the good-faith belief that it is necessary in order to conform to the law. If you have any questions about this privacy statement, please contact our customer service department at [customercare@roveconcepts.com](mailto:customercare@roveconcepts.com) or 800-705-6217
